You
Good
morning from
Switzerland!
Already have these absolutely insane views and I haven't even started hiking yet so off
to a strong start!
It's currently the bank holiday weekend in August, so I planned a super last minute
trip to go hiking because I missed it.
I'm about to do more of a descent hike today just because I haven't been
elevation hiking in a long time and I don't really have my hiking legs anymore,
so I want to ensure I have the stamina to be hiking all three days
I'm here.
There's a really famous mountain hut on this trail and then I'm going to come
back up and the ridgeline and then hopefully hike down and go swimming in the
lake.
Oh I'm in love already.
I
swear
everywhere I turn is more beautiful than the last.
This is absolutely stunning.
We're going up there.
Thank
you.
Single handedly, the most scenic spot I've ever eaten a
cliff bar in my life.
I've reached the peak mountain hut and I just chilled, relaxed for a little bit.
And now I'm going to begin my descent down to the lake so I can
go for a little swim.
The whole reason I actually came on this trip was A, I like to do
at least one solo trip a year.
I've been doing it for the past like four or so years and I just
think they're really fun and a good way to kind of reconnect with yourself.
And the second reason was because I was kind of missing home.
So I'm from Seattle.
The mountains, the lakes, the nature is just absolutely stunning and it's something that you
just really can't replicate unless you're in the mountains.
And I live in London, which is a city and it's flat.
So I decided to book myself a little trip to Switzerland, which is a crazy
thing that I'm able to do.
And the third reason is it was a promotion gift to myself.
I got a promotion at work so I decided to go on a trip to
celebrate and so now I'm eating snacks in the Swiss Alps this
video
does not do it justice this is like steep and tiny and narrow and cliff
facey but at least this is the view
I mean, It does not get better than this.
It doesn't.
Thank you.
There are no real parks in Appenzell like the town so there's not really anywhere
for me to just like pop down and squat and read my books so I'm
just gonna keep wandering.
Thank
you.
you I I
was
just kind of ditzing around just going in between town and back at my Airbnb
looking at webcams looking at cloud covers it was like 1 p.m and I hadn't
done anything all day so I was just like you know what I'm just gonna
go to Wasseren which is where most of the hikes start and then just see
what I'm feeling so I am actually going on a trail back to Sea Police
which is where I was yesterday I'm taking a different way so hopefully we'll get
some different sights and it already looks so different compared to yesterday.
Very moody and I'm very sore as well so it'll be good to get my
legs working again.
I'm already out of breath.
Oh no.
I promise this is only half sweat.
It's also raining but this place is magical.
It literally looks like a storybook.
I'm ready.
God, I love such a nice forest.
With a wheat brown forest all around me, you turned into
a whisper.
Not a soul in my sight could near past the trees.
I was starting to forget you.
And so I woke up this morning And I made my way back to the
city we lived in It's been a while since you packed up Since you laid
down for the world Like a pawn of your plans And I did just the
same Oh, my, I come in a blando
Same lake today, but sitting in a different spot.
I went to one of the local mountain huts And got myself a local beer
and this is quite literally The mountain behind me if you can remember from yesterday,
I think the peaks like right up there But it's actually pretty good There are
these kind of rocky islands within the lake.
I'm just gonna hang out here for a little bit Read my book eat some
snacks before wandering back down And ever since you left I've been bored I've been
sitting on my words like I'm waiting for you to reach right in and pull
them out.
And ever since you left I've been chewing off my tongue trying not to tell
you wrong.
I'm not me since you left me and I'm done.
In an unfortunate twist of events, I slipped and ate shit.
Which I was a little bit concerned about because a doctor has told me I
have really weak bones before and although I take my calcium I landed on an
elbow that I've had a surgery on in the past so I was worried I
might have rebroken something but I thought I'd check it out before hiking down bleeding
like a faucet and it doesn't really hurt too bad it's definitely going to be
a deep bruise and when I put my phone down to get the band-aids out
my phone slipped off the chair and the screen shattered through the screen protector.
But that's fine.
Life happens.
I still had a really amazing day.
So now I'm just gonna hike back to town and just take a chill for
the rest of the night.
come right back
cool, it's fun
good morning from another cloudy day in Appenzell unfortunately the cloud cover is even thicker
and lower than it was yesterday so I've kind of decided that I'm not gonna
hike this morning on the account of that and then also I'm so sore so
instead I think I'm just gonna pack up and spend the day in Zurich Zurich
and please ignore this like glow that's because of the cracks in my phone screen
so ignore that.
I did book an appointment at the Apple in Zurich to get my phone screen
fixed because it's actually cheaper here in Zurich than it is in London which is
kind of surprising to me.
I've been to Zurich before so I've seen all the hot spots so I'm just
going to kind of bop around.
I don't really know what I'm going to do.
Go to chocolate shops?
yeah who knows but I'm gonna pack up and stretch and then catch the train
in
Thank
you.
Take me by the heart